https://acfa-cashflow.com/privacy-policy/

MARKETING POLICY
Welcome to Acfa-Cashflow.com (hereinafter “Company”). To register for Company’s services, you must agree to these Marketing Practices, as well as Company’s Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions of Use.
By registering for Company’s services, you understand that you are requesting a referral for a loan from the independent, participating lenders with whom we may share your information. While our site does not sell your information to vendors not related to your specific application, you are giving your express consent to receive promotional materials from participating lenders. They may also provide information to you about additional services and products. You further understand that all communications, whether to assist you in obtaining the loan requested or for promotional purposes, may be via direct mail, email (at the email address provided by You) and/or telephone/mobile device (at the number(s) provided by you) notwithstanding that your email address and/or numbers may be listed on a corporate, state, or federal Do-Not-Contact registry, suppression list, or the like.
If you do not wish to receive such marketing materials and/or communications, you may request to be removed by using the relevant opt-out mechanism in such communications from third parties. Requests to unsubscribe from receipt of communications from third parties must be communicated directly to such third parties. Company is not responsible for stopping all unwanted communications from sources beyond Company’s control.
PRIVACY POLICY
Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand our online information practices, so that you are able to make an informed and educated decision about how we collect and use your information. While reading through our Policy, it is important to note that any reference to “You” or “Your” refers to you as a user of our online program. Moreover, any reference to “We”, “Us”, “Our” or “Our Website” refers to our Web site.
Please be aware that we will be free to use any and all information that you submit to us through this Website, and for any lawful purpose as explained herein. Please be advised that we collect your information and match you with various lenders, however we are not responsible for the content and/or the privacy practices of lenders sites.
WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT:
We collect all the information you provide to us while on our Website. This includes your name, date of birth, telephone number(s), home address, Email address, Social Security number, employment information, income information, bank account information, personal references, and any other information that you provide to us. We also collect IP addresses, type of Web browser and operating system, type of computer used, and Web page http headers along with information, and all other information relating to the pages our visitors’ access.
This site is intended for you to submit an application in order to receive an immediate loan decision and also to obtain information on loan related products. You must submit the required information to be considered by one of the third party loan providers. Even if you do not complete the full registration process, any personally identifiable information submitted may also be collected for our use.
HOW WE USE COLLECTED INFORMATION:
The information we collect is used to help us determine which loan product may be of interest to you. Your personal, demographic and profile information may be used to help improve our Website, for marketing, editorial, promotional, statistical analysis, and feedback purposes. Any information collected may be added to our databases for the purposes of sending upcoming postal mailings, emails, SMS text-messaging, telemarketing new product information, new service information, site updates and/or status of online orders. Currently we do not utilize these methods of communication with applicants but reserve the right to do so in the future.
Through your use and submission of information on our Website, you agree that even if your number is found on a do-not-call registry, or similar registry, you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section. We reserve the right to share, sell or otherwise disclose your information to third parties. If you utilize our opt out procedures we pass that information on to all third party loan providers that receive your application data for loan eligibility determination. Simply email webmaster@acfa-cashflow.com to opt out.
By providing your personal information, you agree that it may be used for the following purposes: to obtain other information about you from third-parties when the information was improperly or incompletely filled out on our registration form; sharing of your information with trusted third parties such as credit bureaus, affiliated loan providers and/or other financial services providers in accordance with applicable law; considering you for a web site account; and for other marketing products and services that we determine you might find of interest.
We may employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. These companies and individuals have access to our users’ personal information in order to perform their functions for acfa-cashflow.com, but they are not permitted to use our users’ personal information for other purposes. Examples when other companies or individuals may use our users’ personal information may include sending direct mail and email, SMS text-messaging, telemarketing, analyzing data, removing duplicate information from customer lists and providing marketing analysis.
Any and all sensitive Information that we collect from you and from third-parties as part of your loan application, will be used to determine your eligibility for a loan, should you qualify. If you provide personally identifying information, such as your Social Security number, that information may be used to determine your financial status. Upon qualifying for a loan, your loan-specific financial information will be stored and utilized in accordance with the terms of your applicable lender’s Privacy Policy.
If we believe that the service and/or Website is being or has been used in violation of the Website’s Terms and Conditions, or to commit unlawful acts, we reserve the right to release current or past user information under the following circumstances: if the information is subpoenaed; if we are sold or acquired; or when we consider it necessary or appropriate. Furthermore, by agreeing to these conditions, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when we, in our sole discretion, determine the disclosure to be appropriate. This includes, without limitation, sharing your email address with other third-parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and Federal Trade Commission enabling regulations.
Submission of information through your use of our Website means that you agree to receive mobile marketing, including but not limited to text-message based marketing, from us and from our third party advertisers and marketers. Although we do not utilize this currently we retain the right to do so in the future. Even though your mobile telephone number may be listed on state and/or federal do-not-call registries, we retain the right, and you agree that we may contact you via text message based marketing and in accordance with applicable state and federal law. Additionally, your registration and/or use of our Website, amounts to your acknowledgment that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR §310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the “TSR”). If your telephone number is listed at the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, we retain the right and you consent to allow us to contact you via telemarketing, in accordance with the TSR.
HOW WE SAFEGUARD YOUR INFORMATION:
Although no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, we store all information collected in a technically and physically secure environment. While we strive to protect your personal information, you transmit any information at your own risk. We cannot warrant or ensure the security of any information that you transmit. Upon receipt of your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. We strictly limit access to this information only to employees who need the personal information to perform a specific job. Your information is not accessible to the public. In the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information and in compliance with applicable state and federal laws, we will notify you via email along with any applicable regulatory agencies. However, notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.
OUR PROCESS:
After completing the application page you will automatically be redirected to an applicable third party lender’s or seller’s website. As applicable, and in connection with completing your application, we will collect and send your personal information to the respective third party lender or seller. Please note that as a result of your application, you will subject yourself to the third party lender’s or seller’s privacy policy.
YOUR OPT-OUT RIGHTS:
If you want to opt-out from receiving communications from us and/or our third-party partners, please do not submit any of your information to us. When you submit personally identifiable information while visiting our Website, you have automatically opted-in, meaning that you are requesting that we share your personal information with third parties. However, when you receive marketing communications or are otherwise contacted by these third parties, you should directly notify them how you would like you information used and shared by them.
You may opt-out of any additional email communications regarding our Website by sending your request via email or clicking the unsubscribe button. Again, currently we do not use these forms of communications. If a third party is violating our privacy policy or your rights be sure to file a complaint immediately.
OUR PROTECTION OF THE PRIVACY OF MINORS:
We do not permit individuals under eighteen (18) years of age to obtain our products and/or services. If you are under eighteen (18) years of age, do not submit your information as it will be removed from our site immediately.
OUR USE OF PIXELS AND COOKIES:
Our Website pages and/or emails may contain electronic images known as “pixel tags.” These are used to track the pages that our visitors and/or users visit at the Website in order to format future campaigns and upgrade visitor information used in reporting statistics. To help determine the effectiveness of a joint promotional or advertising campaign, Pixel tags from third parties may also be present on our Website
We may use also use “cookies” to help customize your access to our Website. A cookie contains information about you and is stored on your hard drive. We may use cookies to anonymously track and target our users’ interests and to further enhance the experience on our Website. Cookies may also be used for advertising tracking purposes.
OUR RIGHT TO CHANGE OUR POLICY WITHOUT PRIOR NOTIFICATION:
We reserve the right to change our policy at any time and without prior notice to you. Your continued use of our Website, or acceptance of our emails following the posting of changes to this Policy, will mean that you accept any and all such changes and that you agree to continue receiving marketing from us and other third party companies. We reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status and changes to subscriber agreements, Privacy Policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you.
CONTACT US:
Please contact Company directly via email at webmaster@acfa-cashflow.com with any questions or concerns related to these Marketing Practices or your privacy, and/or to opt-out of having your information used by Company for marketing purposes.
Get Started Now!
Terms of Use,
Privacy Policy and
ESIGN Consent
Ready To Grow Your Business? It’s free–prequalify without affecting your credit!
Check Your Options
Copyright © 2020 acfa cashflow | All Rights Reserved
